Search 

[Home](https://www.nextofwindows.com/) Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy
==============

Our website address is: https://www.nextofwindows.com.

**Personal identification information**
---------------------------------------

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, subscribe to the newsletter, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities. We have updated the site with consent management for GDPR compliance as well.

**Non-personal identification information**
-------------------------------------------

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

**Web browser cookies**
-----------------------

Our Site may use “cookies” to enhance User experience. User’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

**Sharing your personal information**
-------------------------------------

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.

**Third party websites**
------------------------

Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website’s own terms and policies.

**Links to Other Websites**
---------------------------

We are not responsible for the practices employed by websites or services linked to or from the Service, including the information or content contained therein. Please remember that when you use a link to go from the Service to another website, our Privacy Policy does not apply to third-party websites or services. Your browsing and interaction on any third-party website or service, including those that have a link or advertisement on our website, are subject to that third party’s own rules and policies. Social Media Widgets: Our Web site includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button and Widgets, such as the Share this button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site. Social Media Features and Widgets are hosted by a third party. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

**Advertising**
---------------

This Site is affiliated with CMI Marketing, Inc., d/b/a CafeMedia (“CafeMedia”) for the purposes of placing advertising on the Site, and CafeMedia will collect and use certain data for advertising purposes. To learn more about CafeMedia’s data usage, click here: [www.cafemedia.com/publisher-advertising-privacy-policy](https://www.cafemedia.com/publisher-advertising-privacy-policy)

**Google Adsense**
------------------

Some of the ads may be served by Google. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to Users based on their visit to our Site and other sites on the Internet. DART uses “non personally identifiable information” and does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, etc. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at http://www.google.com/privacy\_ads.html

### Affiliate Disclaimer

Some of the products mentioned on this site may include an affiliate link and provide the site and its owner(s) and contributes with of monetary earnings. Amazon is an affiliate network we use. When you select a link that goes to Amazon, a cookie may store some data based on your Amazon preferences. You can see Amazon’s privacy notice here [https://www.amazon.com/gp/help/customer/display.html/ref=asus\_gen\_not?ie=UTF8&nodeId=468496&ld=NSGoogle](https://www.amazon.com/gp/help/customer/display.html/ref=asus_gen_not?ie=UTF8&nodeId=468496&ld=NSGoogle)

### Analytics

We use Google Analytics to track the number of users on the site, and which posts they view. You can view the Google Analytics privacy policy at [https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6004245?hl=en](https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6004245?hl=en) The information we collect is used to improve the content of our Web page, used to customize the content and/or layout of our page for each individual visitor, used to notify consumers about updates to our Web site.

Who we share your data with
---------------------------

We have relationships with other companies that we allow to place ads on our Web pages. As a result of your visit to our site, Google, VibrantMedia, and other third-party ad server companies may collect information such as your domain type, your IP address and clickstream information.

* Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site.
* Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to users based on their visit to this site and/or other sites on the Internet.
* Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/).
* Users may opt out of other cookies by clicking [here](https://optout.networkadvertising.org/#!/).

How long we retain your data
----------------------------

If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue. For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.

What rights you have over your data
-----------------------------------

If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.

Where we send your data
-----------------------

Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.

Contact information
-------------------

You may contact us here: nextofwindows.com/contact

Additional information
----------------------

### How we protect your data

We have encrypted the data on this site with SSL for your protection. We have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our site.

### What data breach procedures we have in place

We regularly scan our systems for potential and real data breaches. In the event of a data breach, we will notify our users of the data that was obtained and advise on what action they can take. Upon request we provide site visitors with access to all information \[including proprietary information\] that we maintain about them, unique identifier information (e.g., customer number or password) that we maintain about them, communications that the consumer/visitor has directed to our site (e.g., e-mails, customer inquiries). If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact us at the above addresses.

#### You Might Also Like

* [Please Power Down And Connect The PCIe Power Cables: Fixed on Windows 11](https://www.nextofwindows.com/please-power-down-and-connect-the-pcie-power-cables)

#### Recent Posts

* [Gaming Features Aren’t Available for the Windows Desktop: Best Fixes](https://www.nextofwindows.com/gaming-features-arent-available-for-the-windows-desktop)

Copyright © Next of Windows  
Powered by [ionMag news theme](https://www.wpion.com/free-news-theme/)
